What are your emotions right now,
Antario?
I ain't going to lie. Like I'm just
speechless. I ain't have no words. The
whole phone call I was just shaking cuz
I didn't believe it was real. And then
once like you started talking passing
the phones around and I was hearing
familiar voices, I knew it was real.
How much
prior chats had you had with the
Atlanta?
I talked to the D-line coach. One
second. Let me Let me just put my phone
on DND.
I'm sorry. I'm getting a lot of phone
calls.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh oh my god. Why he keep calling? I'm
sorry.
>> [laughter]
>> One second. I'm coming back. Putting it
on do not disturb.
Oh,
focus.
Sleep. Okay, got it. We good. We good.
We good.
Fix it real quick.
I'm sorry.
I got the phone turned. Okay, got it. We
got it now.
You were talking about like contact you
had with the team before
today. Oh yeah, my bad. Um so when the
call first started, I didn't think it
was real and then they passed it to the
D-line coach Nate. And I ain't going to
lie. Like as soon as I heard his voice
cuz I had a zoom with him few weeks past
before the draft and he was just telling
me all how much he want me there and
just breaking down the scheme and stuff.
So once I heard his voice, it kind of
just confirmed it in my head that it was
real.
How did he outline what they like about
you and how they envision you here?
He just outlined my explosiveness. The
way I played the fastness I play and he
just told me like I fit best in the
scheme and their tech scheme just
getting off the ball and just causing
havoc.
I'm like good.
Just tell us a little bit about your
game. Like what what sets you apart? I
say definitely my violence, my
explosiveness, the way I shed off
blocks,
and the way that I run into ball.
I always was told that you get awarded
running to the ball. So just always made
it a thing of just getting to the ball
because anything can happen.
So then as far as like who you model
your game after, like what's a what's
some player Who are some players in the
NFL that you would say?
I
watch a lot of people. I watch Chris
Jones. I watch Aaron Donald. Like I just
like picking things from their game. And
me I'm not going to say I model my game
out of anybody. I feel like I'm I'm
unique. I feel like I play different in
a lot, but I also try to just get tools
from people in the league from watching
videos and tutorials and stuff like
that.
How much contact did you have with the
Falcons before the draft?
We stayed We stayed mutually close. Like
we were talking.
I had FaceTimes. Had a zoom with the
D-line coach. Had a FaceTime with the
DC. So
we've been talking a lot going into the
draft.
Coach Carroll is a high energy guy,
isn't he?
No, he is.
Had it been more contact the most
contact than other teams of other
I wouldn't
I wouldn't say
it started to become more I'd say more
I'd say previously it was a few others,
but
recently it's been recently it's been
Atlanta.
In 2022, how'd you wind up at Iowa
Western?
I had to go to Juco route coming out of
high school. I came out of high school a
non-qualifier. So I had to go to Juco
and graduate. Spent 2 years there.
What'd you learn about yourself there? I
just learned that I had to figure out I
looked at it as a second chance really.
Knew I wanted to play football, but I
knew I had to get through Juco. So kind
of just put my head down and worked
there. Redshirted the first year.
Started the second year. So just kind of
put my head down and worked there. And I
just found out my ways of learning
and the ways that I do the way I move
best.
Is it accurate you you were
in high school in Iowa for 1 year? Is
that right?
I was there for 4 years. I went to
Dubuque. I was there for 4 years.
But you played football for 1 year? Is
that right?
I so like I started playing football my
freshman year.
Really my freshman year of high school.
I joined the team at 8th grade. Didn't
play. So that's when I first got my
action of team football my freshman year
of high school.
I was
you I guess you weren't much of a
prospect in high school. Like what What
do you think was keeping Were they just
the grades or were there Like do you
think
I'd say like beginning of my football
career I didn't I wasn't who I was now.
I wasn't a violent guy like when it came
to tackling people. I'd hug them like
safely and put them on the ground. So
like I didn't really have that violence
in me.
And that kind of led into it and also
the grade thing. So
my coach I had coach do a good job there
of talking to junior colleges and I went
that route.
So what kind of flipped your switch to
to play with more violence?
I'd say like it kind of flipped my
senior year. I was going through a lot
of family things and football's the only
sport where you can is violent and you
don't you don't go to jail for it. So
kind of started like I kind of started
like practicing and playing with a
little bit more anger. But like as my
college grow, that's when like I mean as
I got into college, that's when my
violence and everything got to this
point.
When you were at Iowa Western, do you
think
if I told you like you're going to be
drafted eventually, would you have would
you have thought? No, I wouldn't have
thought of it all. I mean like to be
honest, football I
I was giving up on football at a point
in my high school. And
head coach which happened and ended up
being one of my advisors and coach
Horner and he was telling the guys to
get me back into football and it was
going into my senior year. And I ain't
going to lie. If it wasn't for him, I
don't know if I would have been playing
football still.